- Oh, excuse me, guys.
哦，不好意思，各位。
I'm just trying to clean.
我只是在打扫。
Hey, can you just stop playing for one second?
嘿，你能暂停一下游戏吗？
- Sure. - One.
当然。
- Done.
好了。
- You know? I'm not complaining or anything.
你知道吗？我没有抱怨或别的意思。
And please, don't stop.
而且请不要停下来。
But, why are you doing all of my work?
但是，你为什么要做我所有的工作呢？
- Can't a kid pitch in once in a while
难道一个孩子偶尔帮忙一下
without being up to something?
就一定有什么企图吗？
- Whenever you're up to something,
- 每当你有什么计划时，
you answer questions with questions.
你总是用问题来回答问题。
- Do I?
- 是吗？
Is that what I do?
我这样做吗？
Don't answer that.
别回答那个。
You know that movie, Clonely Hearts Club?
你知道那部电影《孤独的心俱乐部》吗？
- Where have I heard of that movie before?
- 我之前在哪里听过这部电影？
Oh, yeah, on my shirt!
哦，对了，在我的T恤上！
- You're a clonie?
- 你是个克隆人？
- Total clonie.
- 完全是个克隆人。
"Evelyn could be everywhere she wanted to be..."
“伊芙琳可以去她想去的任何地方……”
- "...except in love."
“……除了爱情。”
[both sighing]
[两人叹气]
- I'm telling you, it's straight.
“我告诉你，这是直的。”
- No, it's not. It's totally askew.
“不，不是的。完全是歪的。”
Look, uh--higher.
“看，呃——更高。”
Higher. Higher.
“更高。更高。”
Lower. Higher.
“更低。更高。”
Higher. Low-higher.
“更高。低-更高。”
- Tom! - Come on!
“汤姆！” “快点！”
What part of higher, higher, lower, higher,
你没听懂什么？更高、更高、更低、更高、更高、稍低一些？
higher, low-higher did you not understand?
- You know, Fan Fest is this weekend.
你知道吗，本周末有粉丝节。
We should totally go!
我们绝对应该去！
All of the stars of the movie will be there.
电影的所有明星都会在那里。
- Uh, hello. That's why I'm doing all the work.
呃，你好。这就是为什么我做所有的工作。
I'm hoping my parents will notice and buy me a ticket.
我希望我父母会注意到并给我买张票。
Oh! Here comes my Dad!
哦！我爸爸来了！
Gotta get noticed!
得让他们注意到我！
- Does that banner look straight to you?
你觉得那横幅看起来直吗？
- Sure. - Wrong answer!
- 当然。 - 回答错误！
It's totally askew!
- 完全歪了！
- Askew...got it.
- 歪了...明白了。
- Did he notice me?
- 他注意到我了吗？
- No, oh, here comes your Mom.
- 没有，哦，你妈妈来了。
- Does that banner look askew to you?
- 那横幅看起来歪了吗？
- Yes. - Wrong answer!
- 是的。 - 回答错误！
It's totally straight!
- 完全直的！
- Hey, boys, does this look straight?
- 嘿，伙计们，这看起来直吗？
- Perfect. - Love it. - You the man.
- 完美。 - 喜欢。 - 你真行。
- Can you at least face this direction?
- 你至少能朝这个方向吗？
- Perfect. - Love it. - You the man.
- 完美。 - 喜欢它。 - 你是老大。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- [whistling melody]
- [吹口哨的旋律]
♪ ♪
[rhythmic clapping] - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
[有节奏的拍手] - ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
- [whistling melody]
- [吹口哨的旋律]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
- ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
- ♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
- Uh...
呃...
So, Mom.
那么，妈妈。
Notice how clean the cafe is?
注意到咖啡馆有多干净了吗？
- I have. It's super clean.
- 我注意到了。非常干净。
Honey, I am so sorry.
亲爱的，我非常抱歉。
I've been so busy organizing this race
我一直忙于组织这次比赛
that I completely forgot to mention
以至于我完全忘记了提到
how helpful you've been lately.
你最近帮了这么多忙。
- [gasps] Oh, you know me,
哦，你了解我的，
always finding ways to be helpful
总是找机会帮忙
with no ulterior motive whatsoever.
没有任何其他动机。
- Well, it hasn't gone unnoticed.
嗯，这没有被忽视。
In fact, I have a little something for you.
事实上，我有点东西要给你。
- [gasps] For me? That is so sweet.
给我？真是太贴心了。
You know, I really wasn't expecting this...
你知道，我真的没想到这个……
Bracelet?
手镯？
Seriously, I wasn't expecting this at all.
说真的，我完全没想到这个。
Thanks, Mom.
谢谢，妈妈。
- Oh, no, that's your "I don't like it" smile.
- 哦，不，那是你的‘我不喜欢它’的微笑。
- Eh, uh, no. It's my "It's really pretty
- 呃，嗯，不是的。这是我的‘它真的很漂亮’
"but I was kind of hoping you would give me a ticket
‘但我有点希望你能给我一张票’
to the Clonely Hearts Club Fan Fest" smile.
‘去《孤独心俱乐部》粉丝节的’微笑。
- Uh, well, this is my
- 嗯，这是我
"I'm sorry but those tickets are $100" smile.
‘我很抱歉，但那些票要100美元’的微笑。
- Who could put a price on my happiness?
- 谁能为我的幸福定价呢？
- Okay, Dawn, I mean, if you don't want the bracelet--
- 好吧，Dawn，我是说，如果你不想要这个手镯——
- Uh, no, no! Mom, I do.
- 呃，不，不！妈妈，我确实想要。
Thanks.
谢谢。
- Okay.
好的。
- Dawn could be everywhere she wanted to be...
Dawn可以去她想去的任何地方...
Except at Fan Fest.
除了Fan Fest。
- Dad!
爸爸！
- What are you doing?
你在做什么？
- Come on!
快点！
- All you guys ever do is
你们这些人总是
sit around playing video games.
坐着玩电子游戏。
You need to get off your butts. Get some exercise!
你们需要站起来。做点运动！
- We're exercising right now!
我们在锻炼呢！
That game gives our finger muscles an excellent workout.
那游戏让我们的手指肌肉得到了极好的锻炼。
- Watch this.
看这个。
[nut cracks]
（坚果裂开声）
- While that's impressive,
虽然那很惊人，
bizarre finger strength is not enough.
但奇怪的手指力量还不够。
You're turning into a bunch of couch potatoes!
你们正在变成一群沙发土豆！
- That's funny because the name of our game is Couch Potatoes!
真有趣，因为我们游戏的名字就叫沙发土豆！
- The object is to load up potatoes with butter,
目标是用黄油、
sour cream, and chives.
酸奶油和细香葱装满土豆。
- Then what?
- 那然后呢？
- Bacon!
- 培根！
- Wow! Stand up.
- 哇！站起来。
[exaggerated straining]
[夸张的用力]
- My hip! [bones cracking]
- 我的髋部！[骨头嘎吱响]
- Was that your bones?
- 那是你的骨头吗？
e got three kids I'm sponsoring a 10k and I
我资助了三个孩子，我参加了一个10公里赛跑，而我
who sound like they need to be oiled.
听起来他们需要上油。
What'll people think?
别人会怎么想？
- Dad, you can't go through life worrying about
- 爸爸，你不能一辈子都在担心
what others think.
别人怎么想。
- Yeah.
是的。
You need to be happy with the guy in here.
你需要对自己满意。
- Wow. You know, you're right.
哇，你说得对。
Sometimes I lose sight of...
有时候我会忽略...
Hey! You're good.
嘿！你很棒。
Here!
这里！
These are Track-N-Fit bands.
这些是Track-N-Fit健身带。
- Can we play games on them?
我们能在上面玩游戏吗？
- No, but you can track your physical activity,
不行，但你可以追踪你的体能活动，
and then the reports get sent to my phone.
然后报告会发送到我的手机上。
- Can we play games on your phone?
- 我们能在你的手机上玩游戏吗？
- No, but if you reach your Track-N-Fit goal for the day,
- 不行，但如果你达到了当天的Track-N-Fit目标，
then you can have your games back.
那你就可以继续玩游戏了。
- Can we play games on them?
- 我们能在它们上面玩游戏吗？
- You're not even listening to me!
- 你根本没在听我说话！
- Just record 10,000 steps a day.
- 只要每天记录一万步。
- 10,000?
- 一万步？
That's like a million!
那简直像是一百万步！
- Did you get your ticket?
- 你拿到票了吗？
- Nope. I got this instead.
- 没有。我得到了这个。
Looks like I'm not going to Fan Fest.
看来我去不了粉丝节了。
- Well, I'm not going if you're not going.
- 好吧，如果你不去，我也不去。
I'm taking a stand!
我要坚持立场！
- I can't let you do that.
- 我不能让你这么做。
- Oh, good! Because I really wanted to go.
- 哦，太好了！因为我真的很想去。
At least you got a fun, festive bracelet.
至少你得到了一个有趣、节日的手环。
- What's festive about it?
- 这有什么节日的？
- Well, it's got knucklebone and niblet beads.
- 嗯，它有指骨和玉米粒珠子。
- Are you just making up words to make me feel better?
- 你是不是只是在编造词来让我感觉好点？
- No. I actually know a lot about making bracelets.
- 不，我其实对制作手链很了解。
I made one just like that. It's pretty easy.
我做过一个一模一样的。挺简单的。
- Can you make me a ticket to Fan Fest?
- 你能帮我做一个去粉丝节的票吗？
- [sighs] [school bell rings]
- [叹气] [学校铃声响起]
I wish. Sorry, Dawn.
我希望可以。对不起，Dawn。
- Let me see that festive bracelet.
- 让我看看那个节日手链。
- Okay...the next person to call this festive is gonna be--
- 好吧...下一个说这是节日手链的人将会是——
free to say whatever she wants.
自由地说她想说的任何话。
Hello, Indra.
你好，Indra。
- I like it! It's shiny!
- 我喜欢！它很闪亮！
You think it would look pretty on me?
你觉得它戴在我手上会好看吗？
- I guess.
我想是的。
- Most people think because I wrestle, I'm all scary.
大多数人因为我会摔跤，就觉得我很吓人。
I love to accessorize!
我喜欢搭配饰品！
What store is that from?
这是哪家店买的？
- [laughs] Uh...I'm not sure.
我不太确定。
My Mom gave it to me.
这是我妈妈给我的。
- Too bad.
太可惜了。
It'd go perfect with my chandelier earrings.
它和我的吊灯耳环会很搭。
- Uh, well, Mae says it's pretty easy to make.
嗯，梅说做起来挺简单的。
- Great! I'll buy this one plus 30 more.
太好了！我要买这个，再加上30个。
- What?
什么？
- They'll make perfect favors
它们会是我生日派对上完美的伴手礼。
for my birthday party.
我的生日派对主题是摔跤！
My theme is take downs!
还有皇冠。
And tiaras.
（笑）我不认为—— - 50美元！
- [laughs] I don't think-- - 50 bucks!
我真的不应该卖我妈妈的——
- I really shouldn't sell my Mom's--
100美元！ - 成交。
- 100! - Sold.
150美元，这是我最后的出价。
- 150, and that's my final offer.
我说了‘成交’。
- I said "Sold."
- 我说了“成交。”
- 200, but that's it.
- 200，但就这些了。
- Wow, that is a lot of money.
- 哇，那可是一大笔钱。
- I installed a lot of sprinkler systems this summer.
- 我这个夏天安装了很多喷水系统。
I've never felt prettier!
- 我从未感觉自己这么漂亮过！
Someone's gonna have a happy birthday!
- 有人要过一个快乐的生日了！
- Someone's going to Fan Fest.
- 有人要去粉丝节了。
[collective sighs and groans]
- [集体叹息和呻吟]
- I can't walk anymore.
- 我走不动了。
- How many more steps do we need?
- 我们还需要走多少步？
- According to the Track-N-Fit,
根据Track-N-Fit的记录，
we have a grand total of 428 steps.
我们总共还有428步。
- Is that close to 10,000?
那离一万步还远吗？
- Only in that it is also a number.
只能说它也是个数字。
- We're never gonna get our games back.
我们永远拿不回我们的游戏了。
- We have to get them back!
我们必须拿回来！
I need to make baked potatoes.
我需要做烤土豆。
- Me too! This morning, I was so desperate,
我也是！今天早上，我太绝望了，
I played an actual potato.
我甚至用了一个真正的土豆来玩。
- Have any of you couch potatoes seen my Clonely Hearts Club DVD?
你们这些沙发土豆有人见过我的《孤独心俱乐部》DVD吗？
- "She was everywhere she wanted to be..."
“她无处不在，她想去的地方...”
- Including under my butt.
“包括在我的屁股下面。”
- Ew! It's all butt warm.
“哎呀！全都是屁股暖的。”
Ew! Ew! Ew! Ew! Ew! Ew!
“哎呀！哎呀！哎呀！哎呀！哎呀！哎呀！”
- I wish we had clones that could walk our steps for us.
“我希望我们有克隆人能替我们走这些步。”
- Look at his little feet go.
“看他那小脚丫走得多快。”
I bet he takes 10,000 steps a day!
“我打赌他一天走一万步！”
- I think we found our clone.
“我想我们找到我们的克隆人了。”
- Are you kidding?
“你在开玩笑吧？”
That dog doesn't look anything like us.
“那只狗跟我们一点都不像。”
- We're gonna have 10,000 steps in no time.
我们很快就能达到一万步了。
- I see virtual potatoes in our very near future, boys.
我看我们不久就会有很多虚拟土豆了，伙计们。
- High five to that!
击掌庆祝一下！
Both: [sigh]
叹气
- Too much work.
工作太多了。
- ♪ ♪
♪ ♪
- Yes.
是的。
- Get ready to hear the best news ever.
准备好听最棒的消息吧。
- Wait...
等等...
Ready!
准备好了！
- I'm going to Fan Fest!
我要去粉丝节了！
- That is the best news ever!
这真是最好的消息！
[both squealing with excitement] We're going to Fan Fest!
我们要去粉丝节了！
How'd you get a ticket?
你怎么弄到票的？
- I sold my bracelet to Indra.
我把我的手镯卖给了Indra。
- Indra? Bought a bracelet?
Indra？买了个手镯？
- She loves to accessorize!
她喜欢装饰自己！
And guess what? She ordered a bunch more.
而且你猜怎么着？她又订了一堆。
- Yay! - So I had enough money
太好了！
to buy my ticket. - Yay!
所以我有足够的钱买票了。
- And we just have to make 30 bracelets by tomorrow.
- 我们只需要在明天之前制作30个手镯。
- Wait!
- 等等！
What?
什么？
That's not enough time.
时间不够。
Just tell her no.
直接告诉她不行。
- I--I can't.
- 我...我不能。
I already spent the money on my ticket,
我已经用那笔钱买了我的票，
the bracelet supplies,
手镯的材料，
and these adorable Clonely Hearts hats!
还有这些可爱的《孤独的心》帽子！
Look, you can be whichever Evelyn you wanna be!
看，你可以成为你想成为的任何一个伊芙琳！
- Dawn, just be honest with Indra.
- 黎明，跟英德拉说实话吧。
What's the worst that could happen?
最坏能发生什么？
- Say it again, Rex!
- 再说一遍，雷克斯！
- I'm scared.
- 我害怕。
- No! The other thing.
- 不！是另一件事。
- Uh, uh, your bracelet's gorgeous.
- 呃，呃，你的手镯真漂亮。
- I've been getting a lot of compliments on the bracelet.
- 我收到了很多关于这个手镯的赞美。
So 30 more by tomorrow, right?
所以明天再有30个，对吧？
- Right...
- 对...
Right?
对吗？
- Wait...
等等...
Right!
对！
- Oh! Here she comes!
哦！她来了！
- You two sure are going to bed early.
你们俩确实要早睡。
- Being a kid is exhausting,
当孩子很累的，
all that learning and growing.
那么多学习和成长。
- Plus all the stress.
再加上所有压力。
Should I play tetherball?
我该玩绳球吗？
Should I not play tetherball?
还是不该玩绳球？
- You know, I loved tetherball.
你知道，我以前很喜欢绳球。
Oh! Funny story!
哦！有趣的故事！
I had this one friend named Heather, and she was a--
我有个朋友叫希瑟，她是——
- Mom! - Oh! Sorry! Yes!
——妈妈！——哦！抱歉！是的！
I'm going. Get some sleep, girls.
我要走了。孩子们，睡个好觉。
[smooching]
[亲吻声]
- It's go time.
开始行动了。
["Eye of The Tiger" by Survivor]
[Survivor乐队的《虎之眼》]
♪ ♪
- [exhausted sigh]
（疲惫的叹息）
Well, it took us two hours. But we did it!
好吧，我们花了两个小时。但我们做到了！
1 down! 29 to go!
1个完成！还有29个！
- We're never gonna finish.
- 我们永远也完不成。
[scratching at door]
[挠门声]
- You hear that?
- 你听到那个了吗？
Oh, hey, buddy. You miss me?
哦，嘿，伙计。你想我了吗？
- Aw, look! He wants a snack.
- 哦，看！他想吃点东西。
- We need the dog. - Why?
- 我们需要狗。 - 为什么？
- It's not important!
- 这不重要！
- What's under the blanket?
- 毯子下面是什么？
- Uh, nothing. Why do you need the dog so bad?
- 呃，没什么。你为什么这么需要狗？
- Nothing!
没什么！
- What sorcery is this?
这是什么魔法？
- We're making bracelets.
我们在做手链。
No big deal.
没什么大不了的。
- Why is the dog wearing your bracelets?
为什么狗戴着你的手链？
- He likes to accessorize!
他喜欢打扮！
- No. I don't think you like to exercise.
不，我不认为你喜欢锻炼。
Look, here's the deal.
听着，事情是这样的。
We need to make 30 bracelets by tomorrow.
我们明天之前需要做30条手链。
We could use some extra hands
我们可以用一些额外的手
and you could use some extra feet.
你也可以用些额外的脚。
What do you say I keep your little secret
我替你保守这个小秘密，
and we work out a little deal?
我们做个小交易如何？
- I don't hate this.
- 我不讨厌这个。
- Neither does he.
- 他也不讨厌。
- We did it, Mae. We made all 30 bracelets
- 我们做到了，Mae。我们做了所有30个手镯
and got a few hours of sleep.
还睡了几个小时。
- Who needs clones when you've got a best friend
- 有了最好的朋友和三个有秘密的兄弟，谁还需要克隆人？
and three brothers with something to hide?
- 早上好！谁想吃早餐？
- Morning! Who wants breakfast?
- 我！
Both: Me!
我们俩都要！
- Hey, where's your bracelet?
- 嘿，你的手镯呢？
- Bracelet?
- 手镯？
Oh! Right.
哦！对。
I know exactly where it is.
我知道它在哪里。
It is...
它就在...
Mae, tell her where it is.
Mae，告诉她手镯在哪里。
- It's at my house. - See! It's at Mae's house.
- 在我家。 - 看！在Mae家。
Mystery solved.
谜团解开了。
- Well, as long as it's safe. It's really valuable.
- 嗯，只要它安全就好。它真的很珍贵。
So! Pancakes?
那么！煎饼？
- W-w-w-w-wait!
等-等-等-等-等一下！
How valuable?
有多贵重？
- Well, I mean, it's not expensive.
嗯，我是说，它不是昂贵的。
It just has a lot of sentimental value.
它只是有很多情感价值。
My Mom gave it to me when I was your age,
我妈妈在我像你这么大的时候给我的，
and when I saw you working so hard, I was so proud of you,
当我看到你这么努力工作时，我为你感到非常骄傲，
I just--I wanted to give you something really special.
我只是——我想给你一些真正特别的东西。
- Why didn't you tell me this the other day?
你为什么前几天不告诉我这个？
- You seemed so disappointed about Fan Fest
你当时对粉丝节似乎很失望
that the Moment was actually kind of ruined.
那一刻实际上变得有点糟糕了。
My only hope is that this bracelet
我唯一的希望是这个手镯
means as much to you as it did when my--
对你来说意义重大，就像当年我——
[getting choked up] When my mother gave it to me.
（哽咽）就像当年我妈妈把它给我时那样。
Ah, I need a tissue!
啊，我需要一张纸巾！
- I am a horrible person.
我是个糟糕的人。
- Don't worry.
别担心。
We'll find a way to get the bracelet back.
我们会想办法把手镯找回来的。
But I gotta ask...
但我得问一下……
Is breakfast happening?
早餐还继续吗？
Is it not happening?
难道不发生吗？
- You think Dad's gonna fall for it?
你觉得爸爸会相信吗？
- Once he sees how many steps we've logged,
一旦他看到我们走了多少步，
he'll have to give us our video games back.
他就不得不把我们的电子游戏还给我们。
- Hey, guys. Your Track-N-Fit stats are through the roof!
嘿，伙计们。你们的Track-N-Fit数据爆表了！
You've each walked 50,000 steps. That's amazing!
你们每个人都走了50,000步。太惊人了！
- Is that all? - I'm not even sore.
就这些吗？
- Yeah. I could do another 50,000 right now.
我甚至都不觉得酸痛。
- Well. You guys have more than earned these back.
是啊。我现在还能再走50,000步。
[reverential gasping]
嗯。你们完全配得上这些。
Not that you'll have much time to play because...good news.
不过你们可能没太多时间玩，因为...好消息。
I signed you up for the Fun Run today.
我给你们报名了今天的趣味跑。
All: What?
所有人: 什么？
- You know how I was embarrassed because I owned
你知道我有多尴尬吗，我开了一家体育用品店，结果有三个沙发土豆。
a sporting goods store, but I had three couch potatoes?
今天...
Well, today...
我从未...
I have never...
如此自豪...
Been more proud...
对那些沙发土豆。
Of those couch potatoes.
[哽咽] 我需要一张纸巾！
[getting choked up] I need a tissue!
趣味和跑步这两个词根本不搭。
- The words "fun" and "run" do not go together.
“乐趣”和“跑步”这两个词放在一起不合适。
- We need to tell the truth.
我们需要说实话。
- Or we can move to India and start new lives.
或者我们可以搬到印度，开始新生活。
They eat with their hands!
他们用手吃饭！
It's a forkless paradise!
这是个不用叉子的天堂！
- I think I have a better idea.
我想我有个更好的主意。
Both: Really?
真的？
- Don't sound so shocked.
别那么惊讶。
- He's right. Let's hear Dicky's idea.
他说得对。我们来听听迪基的主意。
But just in case, we'll keep the India thing in our back pocket.
不过为了以防万一，我们还是把去印度的事放在心上。
- ♪ ♪
♪ ♪
- Here you go!
给你！
- Yes! I love jewelry!
太好了！我喜欢珠宝！
- Me too! And about that bracelet I sold you.
我也是！还有，关于我卖给你的那个手镯。
Wait, where's the bracelet I sold you?
等等，我卖给你的那个手镯呢？
- I sold it.
我把它卖了。
- How could you just sell a bracelet?
你怎么能就这样卖掉一个手镯？
I need that bracelet I sold you!
我需要我卖给你的那个手镯！
- Just make another one.
再做一个不就行了。
- It has to be that exact bracelet.
必须是那个特定的手镯。
- Relax. I sold it to this girl, Emily something.
- 放松。我卖给了一个叫艾米丽的女孩。
But don't worry, she gave me her number.
但别担心，她给了我她的号码。
- [growling] Just text me the number.
- [低吼] 直接把号码发给我。
- Just take my phone!
- 拿我的手机吧！
- ♪ ♪
- Oh, that must be Emily.
- 哦，那一定是艾米丽。
I gotta keep this bracelet exchange as quiet as possible.
我得尽可能低调地处理这个手镯交易。
- Is there a Dawn here?
- 这里有没有叫Dawn的？
I'm supposed to sell her a bracelet.
我应该卖给她一个手镯。
- Shh! Shh! Shh!
- 嘘！嘘！嘘！
I'm Dawn. - Hi!
我是道恩。
I'm--I'm not late, am I?
嗨！
I hate being late.
我——我没迟到吧？
My Mom calls me "Punctual Patty,"
我讨厌迟到。
which is weird because my sister's name is Patty,
我妈叫我'守时帕蒂',
and she's always late, so-- - Yeah, yeah, yeah,
这很奇怪，因为我妹妹就叫帕蒂，
that's great. Okay, come on. Let's go back here
而她总是迟到，所以——
where it's quiet and no one can see us.
嗯，嗯，嗯，不错。好吧，来吧。我们回去
- My Mom gave me that bracelet and I stupidly sold it.
那里安静，没人能看到我们。
I have to get it back.
我妈给我的那手链，我傻傻地把它卖了。我得把它拿回来。
- I don't know. It's kind of my fave.
- 我不知道。它算是我的最爱。
- Please, I'll do anything. Whatever it costs.
- 求你了，我愿意做任何事。无论多少钱。
Just name your price.
只要开个价。
- Well, let's see.
嗯，让我们看看。
You know the movie Clonely Hearts Club?
你知道电影《寂寞芳心俱乐部》吗？
- Know it? I love it.
- 知道吗？我超爱它。
- Love it? I live it.
- 爱它？我活在它里面。
Both: When you're with yourselves, you're never alone.
两人：当你与自己在一起时，你永远不会孤单。
- What I want more than anything is a ticket to Fan Fest.
- 我想要的超过一切的是一张Fan Fest的门票。
- How about a snowboard?
- 滑雪板怎么样？
- No. Fan Fest.
不，是Fan Fest的票。
- Skateboard? - No.
滑板？不。
- Uh...surfboard? Backboard?
呃...冲浪板？篮板？
Any board?
任何板都行？
[sighs] All right.
（叹气）好吧。
- No way!
不可能！
Here!
给你！
- Ah, thank you so much.
啊，非常感谢。
- Thank you!
谢谢你！
This ticket is worth way more than that bracelet.
这张票比那手环值钱多了。
- Not to me.
- 对我来说不是。
Oh, hey Mom!
哦，嘿，妈妈！
Wearing my festive bracelet.
戴着我的节日手镯。
- Here you go, Mrs. Harper. - Thank you, Emily.
- 给你，哈珀太太。 - 谢谢你，艾米丽。
- What sorcery is this?
- 这是什么魔法？
- Well, I know Emily's Mom and we set up a little test.
- 嗯，我认识艾米丽的妈妈，我们设了一个小测试。
- How did you find out?
- 你是怎么发现的？
- I saw Indra wearing your bracelet yesterday
- 我昨天看到因陀罗戴着你的手镯
and then I saw the ticket to Fan Fest in your bedroom
然后我在你卧室里看到了Fan Fest的票
so I put two and two together.
所以我就把两件事联系起来了。
- I'm really sorry, Mom.
- 妈妈，我真的很抱歉。
I was just so focused on getting that ticket
我只是太专注于得到那张票了
I didn't think.
我没有多想。
I never should've sold a gift that you gave me.
我真不应该卖掉你送给我的礼物。
- Hmm... Well.
- 嗯... 好吧。
It makes me proud that in the end,
最终你做了正确的事，这让我感到骄傲。
you did the right thing. - Thanks, Mom.
- 谢谢，妈妈。
And I hope you can find someone to use that ticket.
我希望你能找到人用那张票。
- Hmm, I already have.
- 嗯，我已经找到了。
You earned it.
这是你应得的。
And I wouldn't want Mae to go alone.
我不想让Mae一个人去。
- Thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
- 谢谢！谢谢！谢谢！
Mae, Mae, Mae! Look, look, look! I got the ticket!
Mae, Mae, Mae! 看，看，看！我拿到票了！
I got the ticket! I got the ticket!
我拿到票了！我拿到票了！
[both squealing]
[两人尖叫]
Yes, yes, yes!
是的，是的，是的！
[sighs and groans]
[叹气和呻吟]
- I am so proud of you boys for finishing that race.
- 我为你们完成比赛感到非常骄傲。
- Ah! Not gonna lie, Dad. It was tough.
- 啊！不瞒你说，爸爸。那真的很艰难。
- We just looked at each other and said,
- 我们只是互相看着对方说，
"We're Harpers."
我们是哈珀家的人。
- And Harpers always finish.
哈珀家的人从不半途而废。
- I just wish I could've been out there running with you guys.
我真希望当时能和你们一起跑。
But in a way, I was.
但从某种意义上说，我确实在。
- In--in what way?
在...在什么意义上？
- No, your hats are equipped with tiny cameras
不，你们的帽子装有微型摄像头
that recorded the whole race.
全程记录了比赛。
Let's check the footage, shall we?
我们来看看录像吧，好吗？
Here's you starting the race.
这是你们开始比赛的画面。
And there you are grabbing the bikes you hid in the bushes.
然后你们去拿藏在灌木丛里的自行车。
And here's you riding home.
然后这里是你们骑车回家的画面。
And oh! Oh!
哦！哦！
What sorcery is this?
这是什么魔法？
It's you on the couch playing video games.
这是你在沙发上玩电子游戏的画面。
- Well, time to go "finish" the race.
好吧，是时候去“完成”比赛了。
- [laughter]
[笑声]
- Let's make it look real.
让我们让它看起来真实。
- Hey, when we get back
嘿，当我们回来时
I'll tell Dad "Harpers always finish."
我会告诉爸爸“哈珀家的人总是完成比赛。”
- Good call. He'll eat that up.
好主意。他会喜欢这个的。
- I am beyond disappointed.
我非常失望。
- Wow.
哇。
I thought you'd still be disappointed.
我以为你还会失望。
Glad you're beyond it.
很高兴你已经超越了失望。
- How did you know? - Shh!
你怎么知道的？
He's beyond it.
嘘！
- First of all, your Track-N-Fits all had
他已经超越了。
the exact same number of steps on them.
首先，你们的Track-N-Fits记录的步数完全一样。
And you guys weren't tired this morning,
而且你们今早并不累，
but the dog's looked like that for the last 12 hours.
但狗看起来已经这样12个小时了。
You boys are in a lot of trouble.
你们俩有大麻烦了。
- You can't punish what you can't catch!
你抓不到就惩罚不了！
- Ah!
啊！
- Go, go, go!
快，快，快！
- We're not stopping until you reach 10,000 steps.
你们不停下来，直到达到10000步。
- I knew we should've gone to India.
我就知道我们应该去印度的。
- ♪ ♪
♪ ♪
- [whistling melody]
[吹口哨旋律]
♪ ♪
- [vocalizing]
[发声]
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ 是啊 ♪
[vocalizing]
（发声）
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ 是啊 ♪
- ♪
♪